A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 1 FA1292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowships and Grants, 1951-1996, 2002; 2
  - 64-762-8, 65-834-11, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Lee, An-Shih, 1964-1965 (Box 73, Folder 1226)
  - CM 362-4, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Li, Cheng-bih, 1956, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 1227)
  - 60-541-48, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Liang, Hsu-mu, 1961-1962 (Box 74, Folder 1228)
  - 67-938-60, 69-086-9, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Liang, Mu-lan (Hwang), 1968-1970 (Box 74, Folder 1229)
  - CM 362-5, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Lin, Chi-hsien, 1956-1958 (Box 74, Folder 1230)
  - 63-694-49, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Liu, Ching-hung, 1964, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 1231)
  - 71-203-25, 73-318-2, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Liu, Jiang-chuan, 1972-1973, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 1232)
  - CM 311-16, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Liu, Kwei, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 1233)
  - CM 279-8, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Loo, Chih-teh, 1954 (Box 74, Folder 1234)
  - 59-474-42, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Loo, Chih-teh, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 1235)
  - 57-397-35, 59-474-46, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Lu, Chieh, 1958, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 1236)
  - 62-647-31, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Lu, Hsin-hsiang, 1962-1964 (Box 74, Folder 1237)
  - 61-591-26, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Lu, Kwang-shun, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 1238)
  - 63-694-23, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Lue, Yeh-Bin, 1963, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 1239)
  - CM 311-26, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Ma, Chia-chi, 1957-1958 (Box 74, Folder 1240)
  - CM 362-25, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Mao, Shou-hsian, 1957 (Box 74, Folder 1241)
  - 63-694-43, 64-762-55, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Mao, Wen-ping, 1964-1965 (Box 74, Folder 1242)
  - 57-397-8, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Pan, Foo, 1957, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 1243)
  - 69-086-35, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, P'eng, Fang-ku, 1969-1971 (Box 74, Folder 1244)
  - CM 327-9, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical Center, Fellow, P'eng, Tah-mou, 1955-1957 (Box 74, Folder 1245)
  - 58-429-24, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Shen, Yen, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 1246)
  - CM 362-2, 57-397-10, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Shih, Chun-jen, 1956, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 1247)
  - 73-318-2, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Shin, Yaw-Tang, 1972-1975 (Box 74, Folder 1248)
  - 60-541-43, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Tai, Fu-Hsaing, 1961-1962 (Box 74, Folder 1249)
  - 71-203-16, 73-318-2, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Tan, Karl Kai-Yuan, 1970-1974 (Box 74, Folder 1250)
  - CM 274-12, CM 311-6, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Tan, Tseng-i, 1954-1955 (Box 74, Folder 1251)
  - 64-762-50, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Tang, Chien-Mou, 1965-1966 (Box 74, Folder 1252)
  - 63-694-48, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Tang, Chu-Kuang, 1964-1965 (Box 74, Folder 1253)
  - 69-086-36, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Tang, Kwong-Chou, 1969-1971 (Box 74, Folder 1254)
  - 62-647-29, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Teng, Shu-Wei, 1963-1964 (Box 74, Folder 1255)
  - CM 279-24, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Tien, Ko-kao, 1957-1958 (Box 74, Folder 1256)
  - CM 311-12, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Ting, Nong, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 1257)
  - 61-591-25, 62-647-6, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Ting, Nong, 1961-1963 (Box 74, Folder 1258)
  - 69-086-19, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Ting, Nong, 1969-1971 (Box 74, Folder 1259)
  - CM 241-4, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Tseng, Tse-chung, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 1260)
  - 62-647-15, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Tsou, Chi-shuen, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 1261)
  - 57-397-36, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Tsou, Tien-tseng, 1958-1959 (Box 74, Folder 1262)
  - 60-541-44, 63-694-6, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Tu, Sheng-kai, 1961, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 1263)
  - CM 311-13, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Tu, Yen-chang, 1955 (Box 75, Folder 1264)
  - 67-938-49, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Tung, Yu-ching, 1967-1969 (Box 75, Folder 1265)
  - CM 311-14, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Wang, Chih-fang, 1955 (Box 75, Folder 1266)
  - 63-694-34, 64-762-39, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Wang, Hsueh-shih, 1963-1964 (Box 75, Folder 1267)
  - 57-397-33, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Wang, Shih-Kwei, 1958-1959 (Box 75, Folder 1268)
  - 67-936-5, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Wang, Shih-Kwei, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1269)
  - CM 279-13, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Wen, Chung-chieh, 1954 (Box 75, Folder 1270)
  - 61-591-32, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Wen, Chung-chieh, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 1271)
  - 67-938-68, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Yang, Peter Yun-kuang, 1967-1969 (Box 75, Folder 1272)
  - 61-591-27, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Yang, Shu-tzu, 1962 (Box 75, Folder 1273)
  - 60-541-45, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Yao, Tsyr-shuh, 1961, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 1274)
  - 66-896-20, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Yeh, Ching-Lan, 1966-1968 (Box 75, Folder 1275)
  - CM 259-9, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Yen, Chun Hui, 1953 (Box 75, Folder 1276)
  - 664-762-46, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Young, Tze-kong, 1964-1966 (Box 75, Folder 1277)
  - 59-474-37, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Yu, Chun, 1960-1961 (Box 75, Folder 1278)
  - 57-397-39, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Yu, Jui-chang, 1958-1960 (Box 75, Folder 1279)
  - 64-762-45, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Yu, Jui-chang, 1964-1965 (Box 75, Folder 1280)
  - CM 279-14, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Yu, Ping-shi, 1954 (Box 75, Folder 1281)
  - 62-647-32, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Yu, Shao-chi, 1962-1964 (Box 75, Folder 1282)
  - 70-141-46, 71-203-34, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Yu, Shao-chi, 1971-1973 (Box 75, Folder 1283)
  - 68-011, 69-058, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Visiting Professor, Adler, Richard H., 1968-1969, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 1284)
  - 62-631, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Visiting Professor-Physiology, Brobeck, John R., 1960-1963 (Box 75, Folder 1285)
  - 59-510, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Visiting Professor, Hodges, Paul C., 1959-1960 (Box 75, Folder 1286)
  - 61-599, 62-630, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Visiting Professor, Hodges, Paul C., 1961-1963 (Box 76, Folder 1287)
  - 64-783, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Visiting Professor-Pathology, Jaques, William E., 1964-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1288)
  - 67-974, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Visiting Professor, Liu, Chan-Nao, 1963, 1966-1968 (Box 76, Folder 1289)
  - 65-856, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Visiting Professor, Liu, Chien, 1965-1968 (Box 76, Folder 1290)
  - 70-128, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Visiting Research Fellow, Palmer, Robert H., 1969-1971 (Box 76, Folder 1291)
  - 66-880, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Visiting Professor-Anatomy, Reinhardt, William O., 1965-1967 (Box 76, Folder 1292)
  - 60-526, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Visiting Professor, Strandjord, Nels M., 1960-1962 (Box 76, Folder 1293)
  - 62-668, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Visiting Professor-Pharmacology, van Dyke, Harry B., 1962-1964 (Box 76, Folder 1294)
  - 71-216, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Library Support, 1971-1973 (Box 77, Folder 1295)
  - 72-247 I, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Construction-New Medical Library, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1965, 1972-1974 (Box 77, Folder 1296)
    2014:022, SG 1:060
  - 72-247 I, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Construction-New Medical Library, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1965, 1972-1974; 2014:022, SG 1:060
  - 72-275 I, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1976 (Box 77, Folder 1297)
  - 73-311 I, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Development Audiovisual Program, 1973-1974 (Box 77, Folder 1298)
  - CM 296, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, General Correspondence, 1953-1962, 1968-1969 (Box 77, Folder 1299)
  - CM 295, CM367, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Equipment, 1953-1957 (Box 77, Folder 1300)
  - 58-445, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Equipment, Teaching Facilities, 1958-1961 (Box 77, Folder 1301)
  - 61-610, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Dormitory Furnishings, General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 77, Folder 1302)
  - 63-725, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Reaching Support-Nutritionist & Dietitians, 1963-1964 (Box 77, Folder 1303)
  - 65-818, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Classroom Building Construction, 1960, 1964-1965 (Box 77, Folder 1304)
    2014:022, SG 1:061
  - 65-818, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Classroom Building Construction, 1960, 1964-1965; 2014:022, SG 1:061
  - 71-203-3, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Chao, Ellen Feng-I (Fay), 1966-1967, 1970-1972 (Box 77, Folder 1305)
  - CM 379-4, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Chow, Mei-yu, 1954, 1959 (Box 77, Folder 1306)
  - 57-397-15, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Chow, Mei Yu, 1958, 1960 (Box 77, Folder 1307)
  - CM 296 C, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Chow, Yuan -Wu, 1955-1957, 1959-1960 (Box 77, Folder 1308)
  - 67-938-18, 67-938-66, 67-086-14, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Kao, Li-lan, 1963, 1966-1969 (Box 77, Folder 1309)
  - 61-591-28, 63-694-42, 64-762-48, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Ku, Nai-Ping, 1962-1965 (Box 77, Folder 1310)
  - CM 279-21, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Kuei, Wan-chun, 1954, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 1311)
  - CM 311-15, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Li, Shen-shu, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 1312)
  - CM 259-11, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Liu, Yun-ting, 1952-1953 (Box 77, Folder 1313)
  - 69-086-52, 70-141-38, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Ma, Jan-Ling, 1968, 1970-1972 (Box 77, Folder 1314)
  - CM 279-22, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Nei, Jai-chun, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 1315)
  - CM 296 A, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Sun, Hui-chun, 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 1316)
  - 58-429-25, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Sung, Shen-fan, 1958-1960 (Box 77, Folder 1317)
  - CM 296 D, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Tan, Chang-lei, 1955-1956, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 1318)
  - CM 327-17, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Tao, Bi-hwan, 1956, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 1319)
  - CM 296 E, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Wang, Bette Wei, 1956-1959, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 1320)
  - 57-397-37, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Wang, Shih-hsi, 1957-1959, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 1321)
  - CM 296 B, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Wang, Shih-jung, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 1322)
  - 57-397-38, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Yang, Hsia-fang, 1957-1958, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 1323)
  - 67-938-70, 68-022-55, 69-086-63, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Yang, Ping-hui Hsia, 1967-1970 (Box 78, Folder 1324)
  - CM 327-26, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Fellow, Yu, Tao-chen, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 1325)
  - 69-070, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Visiting Professor, Mandrillo, Margaret P., 1964-1965, 1967-1973 (Box 78, Folder 1326)
  - CM 247, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing School, Visiting Professor, Hodgman, Gertrude E., 1952-1953, 1956-1957 (Box 78, Folder 1327)
  - 59-513, Kaoshiung Medical College (Formerly Takau Medical College), Books, 1959-1963 (Box 78, Folder 1328)
  - CM 290, National Taiwan University (NTU), Books & Journals, 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 1329)
  - CM 346, National Taiwan University (NTU), Books & Journals, 1955-1960 (Box 78, Folder 1330)
  - CM 313, National Taiwan University (NTU), Equipment-Surgical Laboratory, 1954-1955 (Box 78, Folder 1331)
  - CM 347, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment, 1955-1958 (Box 78, Folder 1332)
  - 58-426, National Taiwan University (NTU), Equipment-Physiology Department, Teaching AIds, 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 1333)
  - 58-446, National Taiwan University (NTU), Health Training Center Personnel, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 1334-1335)
  - 58-456, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment, 1958-1961 (Box 78, Folder 1336)
  - 59-485, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Cardiopulmonary Diagnostic Laboratory, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 1337)
  - 59-512, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Workshop, 1959-1962 (Box 78, Folder 1339)
  - 60-527, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Library Support, 1961-1964 (Box 78, Folder 1340)
  - 60-528, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Radiology, 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 1341)
  - 60-561, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Hematology, 1960-1963 (Box 79, Folder 1342)
  - 61-574, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Cardiac Surgery, 1960-1964 (Box 79, Folder 1343)
  - 61-611, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Physiology, 1961-1962 (Box 79, Folder 1344)
  - 61-612, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Research Equipment, 1961-1964 (Box 79, Folder 1345)
  - 62-632, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment & Furnishings-Library, 1961-1964 (Box 79, Folder 1346)
  - 62-653, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Cardiac Surgery Research Center-Construction & Equipment, 1962-1964 (Box 79, Folder 1347)
    2014:022, SG 1:062
  - 62-653, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Cardiac Surgery Research Center-Construction & Equipment, 1962-1964; 2014:022, SG 1:062
    Oversized architectural drawings (3)
  - 62-669, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment, 1962-1964 (Box 79, Folder 1348)
  - 63-727, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Building Construction-Laboratory & Classroom, 1963-1967 (Box 79, Folder 1349)
  - 64-749, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Physical Medicine & Rehabilitation, 1964, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 1350)
  - 64-751, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Cardiopulmonary, 1964-1966 (Box 79, Folder 1351)
  - 64-772, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Library Support, 1964-1968, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 1352)
  - 66-867, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Cardiac Surgery, 1965-1966 (Box 79, Folder 1353)
  - 66-884, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Toxicology Laboratory, 1965-1967 (Box 79, Folder 1354)
  - 66-885, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Microbiology Teaching Program, 1966-1967 (Box 79, Folder 1355)
  - 66-886, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Central Research Laboratory, 1966-1968 (Box 79, Folder 1356)
  - 66-915, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment, 1966-1967 (Box 80, Folder 1357)
    2014:022, SG 1:063
  - 66-915, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment, 1966-1967; 2014:022, SG 1:063
  - 67-975, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Library Support-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1967, 1969-1972 (Box 80, Folder 1358)
  - 67-948, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment, 1967-1969 (Box 80, Folder 1359)
  - 67-977, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Pathology-Blood Bank-Cardiopulmonary, 1967-1968 (Box 80, Folder 1360)
  - 68-013, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Radiology, General Correspondence & Original Requests, 1968-1970 (Box 80, Folder 1361)
  - 68-041, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Clinical Diagnostic Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1970 (Box 80, Folder 1362)
  - 68-042, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Pharmacology, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1967-1969, 1971, 1973-1974 (Box 80, Folder 1363)
  - 68-043, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Research-Biochemistry, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 1364)
  - 69-071, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 1365)
  - 69-073, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1970, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 1366)
  - 69-074, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Teaching Programs-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1959, 1968-1970, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 1367)
  - 69-104, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Research, 1969-1972 (Box 80, Folder 1368)
  - 70-129, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1972 (Box 80, Folder 1369)
  - 70-130, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 1370)
  - 70-159, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Cardiopulmonary, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1972 (Box 80, Folder 1371)
  - 70-160, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1972, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 1372)
  - 71-185, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Otorhinolaryngology, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 1373)
  - 71-186, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1974 (Box 81, Folder 1374)
  - 71-204, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Continuing Medical education-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1975 (Box 81, Folder 1375)
  - 71-217, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 81, Folder 1376)
  - 71-218, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1974 (Box 81, Folder 1377)
  - 64-784, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment, 1964, 1966, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 1378)
  - 64-785, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Central Research Laboratory, 1964-1965, 1967, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 1379)
  - 66-916, 67-976, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-Clinical Diagnostic Building, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1965-1968 (Box 81, Folder 1380)
  - 68-012, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment, 1968-1969 (Box 81, Folder 1381)
  - 69-103, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment, 1969-1970 (Box 81, Folder 1382)
  - 70-158, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1972 (Box 81, Folder 1383)
  - 72-249 I, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, School of Rehabilitation-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1974 (Box 81, Folder 1384)
  - 72-250 I, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1975 (Box 81, Folder 1385)
  - 72-251 I, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Library Support-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1977 (Box 81, Folder 1386)
  - 72-277 I, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Clinical Diagnostic Building-Equipment, 1972-1975 (Box 81, Folder 1387)
    2014:022, SG 1:064 2014:022, SG 1:065
  - 72-277 I, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Clinical Diagnostic Building-Equipment, 1972-1975; 2014:022, SG 1:064
  - 72-277 I, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Clinical Diagnostic Building-Equipment, 1972-1975; 2014:022, SG 1:065
  - 72-278 I, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972, 1974-1977 (Box 81, Folder 1388)
  - 72-279 I, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1974 (Box 81, Folder 1389)
  - 73-313 I, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Supplies & Equipment/Surgery-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1973-1974 (Box 81, Folder 1390)
  - 73-314 I, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 1391)
  - 72-280 I, National Taiwan University (NTU), Public Health, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1973 (Box 81, Folder 1392)
  - 72-266-31, 72-318-1, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medicine, Fellowship Allocation, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 1393)
  - 72-266-32, 73-329-32A, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medicine, Fellowship Allocation, 1974-1979 (Box 82, Folder 1394)
  - 72-266-33, National Taiwan University (NTU), Nursing, Fellowship Allocation, 1974, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 1395)
  - 71-187, National Taiwan University (NTU), Public Health, Public Health Nurse Training Scholarships, 1969, 1971-1972 (Box 82, Folder 1396)
  - CM 311-24, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Fellow, Chang, Wen-pin, 1955-1957 (Box 82, Folder 1397)
  - 68-022-21, 69-086-26, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medical School, Fellow, Chen, Chiop-Chiang, 1968-1970 (Box 82, Folder 1398)